Really, this is starting to annoy me.
Why do you insist on struggling when
there is nothing to gain from it?
It should be obvious by
now that you have lost.
Why do you choose to resist
when the outcome is clear?
Your actions are meaningless.
Whether we choose to die on our
knees or with a sword in our hand,
it's our actions that count.
That's what being human's about.
You prefer black like a knight
from the dark territory?
Well boy if you wish to
continue suffering so
then i shall make yours
very long and cruel!
Beyond anything you can
imagine you'll be in
such misery you'll be
begging me for death!
That won't be enough to
make up for my stupidity.
It's a dream of a blue light.
Let's go back
to the moon.
Your voice has no place in place.
No one has taught me.
It's a rule.
When i was young i was strong.
I hope you've been here for a long time.
The journey of the time is coming.
I'm not going to be a time.
I'm falling into the ceiling.
I'm falling into the
dark. I'm a bright light.
I'm passing through the light.
I'll see you
next time.
The high Norkia style.
She's going to try and
kill me with one strike.
Ah!
Yes, a one-handed four-hit sword skill.
It's called vertical square, is it not?
Sword skill?
How'd she know that term?
Maybe she got it from Eugeo's memories.
Alright, I'll use something
I never showed him.
A combo with more than four hits!
Mine was a six-hit skill
called Crucifixion.
No way.
A one-hit skill, Sugou.
There is nothing I do
not know about the system
which drives the properties
of this world. Damn it.
That's not like you.
You chill.
Kirito.
Integrity knights aren't
the only ones who lost
their memories we did too
something very important.
You Alice and I were born and ruled
and grew up together remember?
Yeah I remember it now.
I was right there with you in
the square when Alice was taken.
I couldn't move.
I felt so helpless, but not you.
You were so brave.
You charged in and stood up to that night.
You, too.
This time, I'm going to help you
like I should have back then.
This time, we'll save Alice. Come on.
Kirito, on your feet, you can do it.
Stand up as many times as it takes.
You can do it.
Get up, my best friend.
My hero.
Him, for you, I'll stand
as many times as it takes.
Honestly, you have lost.
Why do you continue to resist?
Because I can.
It's why I'm still here.
And I won't stop till you're gone.
This world belongs to me.
How dare you come here
uninvited and defy my rule?
On your knees!
Offer your head to me!
Accept your defeat!
No way.
You're not a ruler. You're a thief.
You don't love this world or
the people who live in it.
So you have no right to be in charge.
To love is to rule.
And I love everything.
And rule everything.
How dare you!
Curse you!
Not yet.
Not yet!
In the end, neither sword was metal.
How foolish.
I did not expect this outcome.
Even if I gathered up every spatial resource
here, my wound is too great to heal.
At this point, I have no choice.
Wait, where are you?
It is much earlier than I had planned.
Nevertheless, it is time for me to go.
Farewell, little boy.
For now, the next time we meet,
shall be in your world.
What? No!
Your remnants!
Don't leave me here!
Take me with you!
I know you, Cretan!
Let me go this instant!
At last, I can become one with you!
You're ravening!
You disgusting clown! No! No!
My administrator!
My lady!
I did love it.
I loved all of it.
It's over.
Yu-Gi-Oh.
Please work.
Stop bleeding.
Hail goddammit!
Come on.
You can't die.
Yu-Gi-Oh.
Stay cool.
Kirito.
Yuju, let go.
Come on, I'm trying to heal you.
Don't bother.
It's fine.
Really.
Leave it.
What are you saying?
I'm not gonna let you die!
No, this is for the best.
It has to be.
Otherwise, you and I...
We would have fought over Alice.
Me?
To get back the memory of the Alice I knew
and you to save Alice the Night's soul.
Then get up and fight!
I'm gonna heal you and
then then we'll fight!
You're way stronger than me! Do it!
Do it for the old Alice's sake!
Fight me!
I can't fight with a broken sword.
Besides, I was weak.
and gave in to Administrator.
I tried to kill you.
This is how I can pay for that sin.
Like I care!
You weren't in your right mind anyway!
You fought back and snapped yourself
out of it like the badass you are!
If it wasn't for you, we
couldn't have beat Administrator.
So you got nothing to feel guilty about!
You got nothing to pay for!
I wish that were true.
I always wished I could be more like you.
You're so brave, and everyone loves you.
I bet Alice does, too.
You...
Now I know.
Love isn't something you get.
It's something you give.
Alice taught me that.
I don't see you working.
Look, I'm almost done
making my part of it.
How far did you get?
I'm way further along than you.
The guard's all that's left.
Then let's stay here and keep
working until we finish it.
But like, what if he comes looking?
Let's go back.
But we're almost finished.
Let's stay.
Just a bit longer. Please?
Okay.
You win, but we should
still hurry it up. Mm-hmm.
All done!
So am I.
Wait, you've been here this whole time?
What you two doing?
Um, nothing.
It's three days too early, but oh well.
Happy birthday, Eugeo!
Is that for me?
It's no match for the real thing,
like the one your big brother's got.
Still, this one's better than any of the
wooden swords the shop and town carries.
It's wonderful.
It's beautiful.
I'll take good care of it.
Thank you both.
I never got a birthday gift
that made me so, so happy.
What are you crying for?
I wasn't!
See?
Wait!
Us three grew up together,
and we're the best of friends.
We're going different ways now,
but our memories will live forever.
We'll be with you, forever.
You see?
It's fine.
So don't cry, Kirito.
Well, like you said, you're not gone.
You'll be here forever.
Forever and ever.
The best of... ...friends.
Kirito, you there?
Where'd you go?
I'm here. I'm right here.
Oh, I see now.
Stars sparkling in the dark.
The night sky above the Giga
Cedar was full of stars.
Your sword sparkles like that.
Hey, how's that for a name?
Call it the Night Sky Blade.
Yeah, that's a good one.
Thank you, Ujiyo.
You're like the night sky,
wrapping this sorry world in your stars.
I guess this is for the best, huh? It is.
We can leave the rest to those two now.
I'm sure they'll guide the
world in the right direction.
Okay.
Well then, you ready?
Yes.
Thank you.
Kick-Walka!
Kick-Walka! Kick-Up!
TIGUOKA!!!
Lieutenant Colonel, the
door's been breached.
We have to leave.
They'll be in the control room any second.
I'm shutting the bulkhead.
No, wait!
Just give me a couple minutes.
I have to sort a few things out here.
What the...?
Higa, how long till we're locked down?
I need another 80...
No, 70 seconds! What?
Holy crap!
Hey, Keeks, it's a call
from the Underworld.
It's...
Dude, it's him!
It's Kirigaya! What? Really?
Kirito! Stop!
Come in, Kirito! Are you there?
Yeah, I'm here.
You know what you've done?
Huh?
You son of a bitch!
Can we please save the insults for later?
Right now, I need you
to listen to me. What?
I hear shooting.
What's going on?
I can't get into that right now.
Now, listen, Kirito.
I need you to locate a girl named Alice.
Find her and take her to - I
don't have to look for her.
She's right here.
You have her?
You gotta be kidding.
That kid's awesome.
Yeah.
All right, once we're off the line,
I'll crank the FLA to a thousand.
Then take Alice and head
to the world's end altar.
I never heard of that place. That's okay.
Just go out the eastern gate
and the altars due south.
Sir!
Two of them are heading down the corridor.
Port electric! What?
Be careful.
We just need the mains off.
Whatever you do, don't damage the
lines for the light cube cluster.
Would you relax, bro?
I know what to cut.
We're screwed!
What do we do?
If they cut the main power line
now, it's gonna cause a surge!
The light cube cluster should be safe,
but the subcomputer where
kitty guy's STL is won't be!
The surge will cook as Fluctlight!
Okay, I'll handle the lockdown.
Higa, take Dr.
Kojiro and Asuna and
get to the upper shaft.
Keep Kirito safe.
Asuna?
What the hell?
What's she doing at RAF?
They're cutting the power!
The screw propellers are going down!
Kirito!
Oh, Siune!
So this is me,
I'm going to take a long way to walk.
I've been walking without
a long way to walk.
I want to protect,
I want to take a long way
to take a long way to walk.
I'm not going to take
a long way to walk.
Oh, everything turns to ash to ash.
And everything turns to dust to dust.
So get me now!
I love you, I love you.